A Guide to the Louis O. Kunkel papers, Rockefeller University Faculty FA172
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Correspondence, 1930-1959; 3
  - Bo (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Borodin, D., 14. items
      Includes Borodin bibliography and curriculum vitae.
    - Bos, L., 2 items
    - Boston City Hospital, 2 items
      Recommendation for J.C. Shull.
    - Botanical Review, 1934-1945; 17 items
      Correspondence about Kunkel contributions (1935; 1945) "virus diseases of plants".
    - Botanical Society of America, 7 items
      Correspondence with Gleason, Hopkins, Creighton and Fuller concerning membership.
    - Boughton, D.C. Lecture, 1934-1948; 11 items
      Includes: Athens, Ga. Univ. of Ga. Biology Division lecture, 7 May 1937.
    - Bountiful Ridge Nurseries, 1 item
    - Bowen, P.R., 3 items
    - Bowles, G.T., 2 items
      Evaluation of E.M. Hildebrand
    - Boyce Thompson Institute for Plant Research (Miscellaneous), 1932-1946; 47 items (Box 5, Folder 5)
      Miscellaneous correspondence. Correspondence with B.M. Brooks includes typescripts of Kunkel abstracts.
      See also Crocker box no. 6, Beale box no 4, Zimmerman box no. 16, Arthur box no. 4.
      - Barton, L.V., 5 items
      - Brooks, B.M., 18 items
      - Granger, R.G., 3 items
      - Johnson, M., 9 items
      - Knapp, H., 1 item
      - Troy, Z., 11 items
  - Bo-Bu (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Boyd, G.H., 1937 May 7; 5 items
      Meeting: University of GA. Biologists meeting. Paper delivered "New views in plant virus disease research.
    - Boyd, O.C., 2 items
    - Boyd, Wm., 2 items
    - Boyer, C.A., 2 items
    - Boyle, J.S., 5 items
    - Bradford, F.C., 1 item
    - Bradley, R.H., 2 items
    - Bramhall, Dean Co., 1 item
    - Branch, F.H., 2 items
    - Brandes, E.W., 1932-1949; 15 items
      Meeting. Includes International Soc Sugar Cane Technologists Congress. Paper delivered on "virus diseases", 1938 Oct/Nov.
    - Brecher, S., 2 items
    - Bretz, T.W., 1937-1946; 10 items
    - Bretzloff, W. Jr., 2 items
    - Bridgman, S., 1 item
    - Brierley, P., 1933-1955; 18 items
      Includes Correspondence about 1953 Yearbook of U.S. Dept of Agriculture manuscript on Aster yellows.
    - Brookhaven National Laboratories. Meeting, 1953 August 3-5; 13 items
      Correspondence with Sparrow, Kuper, Koshland and Caldecott about Brookhaven National Laboratory Summer Conference. Paper delivered "virus induced abnormalities" and Discussions.
      Includes proposed outline of speakers and topics.
    - Brooklyn Botanical Gardens., 2 items
      On attending 25 anniversary of establishment of
    - Brown Bros. Mfg. Corp., 2 items
    - Bruehl, G.W., 2 items
    - Bruner, S.C., 3 items
    - Bryan, M.K., 4 items
    - Bucha, H., 2 items
    - Buchwald, N.F., 2 items
    - Bufano, D.J., 2 items
    - Buggs, C.W., 3 items
    - Burlington Hotel, 1 item
    - Burnett, G., 2 items
    - Burt, E.A., 1 item
    - Butler, E.G., 1940-1947; 10 items
      Includes comments on developing plant science program at Princeton; member of Advisory Council of Biology dept at Princeton and attends meetings.
    - Butts, J.S., 2 items
      Comments on G.W. Cochran research proposal on plant viruses
  - C-Ca (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Cadman, C.H., 4 items
    - Caldis, P.D., 1 item
    - Caldwell, J., 9 items
    - Caldwell, R.M., 14 items
    - California Agricultural Experiment Station, 4 items
    - California Nursery Co., 3 items
    - California, University of, Library, 4 items
    - Calvert, O.H., 6 items
    - Campbell, C.I., 3 items
    - Canada Department of Agriculture, 5 items
    - Capoor, S.P., 2 items
    - Cardona, C., 2 items
    - Carlay, P., 2 items
    - Carlton Hotel, 1 item
    - Carmody, J., 2 items
    - Carrington, E.S., 2 items
    - Carsner, E., 1931-1952; 20 items
      Professional Correspondence between colleagues. Meeting:.
      Includes 1932 Apr RI staff meeting. Paper delivered "Some types of plant viruses".
    - Carter, E.A., 2 items
    - Carter, J.C., 3 items
    - Carter, W., 1932-1947; 30 items
    - Professional Correspondence between colleagues
      Includes Carter holographs.
  - Ca-Ch
    - Cartledge, J.L., 2 items (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Casals, J., 1947 February 21; 2 items (Box 5, Folder 8)
      Meeting: NYC RIMR staff meeting. Paper delivered "Corn stunt disease"
    - Casazza, E., 2 items (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Caspersson, T., 14 items (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Cassell, R.C., 2 items (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Castillo, B.S., 2 items (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Cation, D. Professional, 1934-1949; 35 items (Box 5, Folder 8)
      Professional Correspondence between colleagues. Manuscript. Includes Correspondence about ms "Peach yellows" for Handbook of Virus Diseases of Stone Fruits in North America; photographs of diseased and recovered trees; Cation holograph (See also: Gravatt, A.R. Box no. 7).
    - Cattell, J.M. [Editor, Science] Manuscripts, 7 items (Box 5, Folder 8)
      Includes Correspondence about mss "The action of high frequency sound waves on tobacco mosaic virus"; "False blossom in periwinkles and its cure by heat" and book review of "Plant viruses and virus diseases" by F.C. Bawden.
    - Cattell, J. [Editor: American Men of Science], 4 items (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Cattell, W., 2 items (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Cayouette, R., 4 items (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Cavanagh, A.E., 4 items (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Cejp, K., 1 item (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Central National Bank, 2 items (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Chamberlain, G.C., 1 item (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Chamberlain, J.M., 2 items (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Chambers, E.L., 2 items (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Chandler, C., 2 items (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Chandler, F.B., 2 items (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Chandler, S.C., 2 items (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Chapman, R.S., 1 item (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Chatterjee, N.C., 2 items (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Chen, S.T., 5 items (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Cheo, C.C., 2 items (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Chessin, M., 9 items (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Chester, Kenneth S., 1933-1950; 85 items (Box 5, Folder 9)
      At RIMR 1933-1937. Includes Chester holographs and professional correspondence. between colleagues.
  - Ch-Co (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Chetty, C.V.S., 2 items
    - Chickering, H.T., 1 item
    - Childers, N.F., 2 items
    - Chilean Nitrate Educational Bureau, 2 items
    - Christensen, H.C., 2 items
    - Christensen, J.J., 1939 1950-1953; 7 items
    - Christie, K., 4 items
    - Chronica Botanica, 1935 1949; 11 items
      Includes typescripts of 1935, 1936, 1937/38, 1938/39 reports from RIMR Division of Plant Pathology and F.O. Holmes abstract.
    - Chrysler, M.A., 1 item
    - Chupp, C., 1935 1942; 9 items
    - Church, M.B., 2 items
    - Cinis, P.H., 5 items
    - Clark, E.S., 4 items
    - Clark, H.E., 2 items
    - Clark, N., 2 items
    - Cleland, R.E., 12 items
      Manuscript: Includes 1 item about ms "Heat cure of aster yellows in perwinkles" for American Journal of Botany and comments as member of Botanical Section, National Academy of Sciences.
    - Clinch, P., 1 item
    - Clum, H.H., 4 items
      Manuscript: About ms "Viruses in relation to the growth of plants". Published in Torreya
    - Cochran, G.W., 1946-1948; 37 items
      At RIMR.
  - Co (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Cochran, L.C., 1931 1951; 30 items
      - Meeting, 1944 December 9-11
        Includes 1944 Dec 9-11 Cincinnati, Ohio American Phytopathological Society meeting. Paper delivered on Herbaceous hosts of the disease of peach.
    - Cohen, M., 2 items
    - Cohen, S., 1 item
    - Cohn, A.E., 5 items
      Includes Correspondence about attending dinners honoring Dr. Van Slyke and Dr. and Mrs. Simon Flexner. 1 Cohn holograph.
    - Colacicco, G., 2 items
    - Coleman, J.L., 2 items
    - Collens, J., 1 item
    - Collier, P.F. & Son Co., 11 items
      On articles for Collier Encyclopaedia
    - Colorado Agricultural Experiment Station, 1 item
    - Columbia University, 1932-1959; 13 items
      Member of W.C. Price thesis examining committee; attendance at commencements.
    - Compton, A.H., 1 item
      Recommendation for G.H. Godfrey for AAAS grant
    - Conant, James B., 1932-1934; 6 items
      Recommendation for Philip White with White biographical material. Includes Conant recommendation for S.E. Kamerling (at RIMR 1932-1934).
    - Conrad-Pyle Co., 3 items
    - Connecticut Agricultural Experiment Station, 2 items
    - Conners, I.L., 3 items
    - Conover, D., 2 items
    - Cook, M.T., 1933-1942; 19 items
    - Cook, O.F., 1 item
  - Co-Cu
    - Coolidge, Shepley, Bullfinch & Abbott, 14 items (Box 6, Folder 3)
      Correspondence with architects about setting up laboratories and greenhouses
    - Coons, G.H., 1933 1947; 10 items (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Cooper, V.I., 2 items (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Corbett, M.K., 10 items (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Cornell Agricultural Experiment Station, 1 item (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Cornell University, Dept of Plant Pathology, 1 item (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Cornell University Press, 1 item (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Corner, G., 2 items (Box 6, Folder 3)
      Includes Correspondence between W.J. Robbins and P.R. White with handwritten note by Kunkel on White's use of method of root excision.
    - Corp, V.H., 2 items (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Cortright, C., 2 items (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Corwin, J.H., 2 items (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Costa, A.S., 1942 1948; 28 items (Box 6, Folder 3)
      Includes recommendation for and on Rockefeller Foundation fellowship.
    - Cottini, L., 1 item (Box 6, Folder 3)
      Recommendation for
    - Cotton, T.L., 2 items (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Couch, J.N., 2 items (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Coughlin, A., 2 items (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Coulson, J.G., 1934 April 18; 6 items (Box 6, Folder 3)
      Meeting. Includes 1934 Apr 18 Annual meeting of Quebec Society for the Protection of Plants. Paper delivered "Recent advances in the study of plant virus diseases".
    - Coulter, C.B., 2 items (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Coutelen, F., 1 item (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Cowdry, E.V., 2 items (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Cross, C.E., 4 items (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Crossley, A.M. Mrs, 1938 February or March 21; 2 items (Box 6, Folder 3)
      Meeting: Princeton, N.J. Women's College Club meeting. Paper delivered "Keeping plants well".
    - Culbertson, R.E., 2 items (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Cunnius, N., 5 items (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Cunningham, J.D., 1 item (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Crocker, Wm. (Director, Boyce Thompson Institute), 1931-1948; 28 items (Box 6, Folder 4)
      Professional Correspondence between colleagues socially friendly. Meeting.
      Includes Correspondence about 1933 Dec 8 American Institute Junior group meeting. Paper delivered "Filterable viruses or ultra-microscopical disease producers".
  - D-De (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Dalmat, H.T. Seminar: University of Pennsylvania Botany seminar "of the use of dodder in plant virus research", 1952 March 25; 2 items
    - Danforth, R.E., 2 items
    - Darken, M.A., 3 items
    - Darker, G.D., 2 items
    - Darrow, G.M., 1934 1951; 10 items
      Includes recommendation for W.C. Price.
    - Das, C.R., 2 items
    - Das, Gupta, 13 items
    - Davey, P.H., 2 items
    - Davidson, O.W., 5 items
    - Davies, E., 2 items
    - Davis, C.C., 2 items
    - Davis, D., 2 items
    - Davis, G.N., 18 items
    - Davis, M.B., 1 item
    - Dawson, J.C., 2 items
    - Day, H.W., 1 item
    - Day, M.F., 2 items
    - Day and Zimmerman, 10 items
      About government scientific consultant work. Includes handwritten Personnel Security Questionnaire for top secret clearance and biographical material.
    - Dean, E.G., 2 items
    - Delladonna, J.V., 2 items
    - DeLong, D.M., 1 item
    - Denisen, E.L., 1 item
    - Dennis, R.W.G., 1 item
    - Denny, F.E., 2 items
  - deR-Do (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - deRopp, R.S. 1945-1951. At RIMR 1945-1946, 35 items
      Includes recommendation for.
    - Desjardins, P.R., 3 items
    - Deuber, C.G., 2 items
    - Diachun, S., 1 item
    - Dickman, S.R., 2 items
    - Dimock, A.W., 4 items
    - Dimond, A.E., 1939 1952; 2 items
      Includes RIMR contribution to Phytopathology.
    - Dobroscky, I.D. (Mrs. C. Van de Water), 1931-1948; 15 items
    - Dochez, A.R., 1 item
    - Dodds, H.W. (President, Princeton University), 4 items
      On election to membership on the Advisory Council of Dept of biology, Princeton University
    - Doerr, R. Manuscript, 1936-1950; 25 items
      Includes chapter "General pathology of virus infections in plants" for Handbook of Virus Research; ms "Studies on a new corn virus disease" for Archiv fr die gesamte viros-forschung.
    - Dole, V.P., 1 item
    - Dorsey, M.J., 2 items
  - Do-Du
    - Dorst, H.E., 2 items (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Doty, H.S., 2 items (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Douglas, A. Jr. (State Assembly), 1 item (Box 6, Folder 7)
      On favoring passage of the Medical Research Pound Law
    - Douglass, J.R., 1 item (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Dounine, Dr., 5 items (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Dover, C., 3 items (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Dow Chemical Co., 2 items (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Dow, R.B., 1 item (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Doyle, E., 2 items (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Drain, B.D., 7 items (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Drayton, F.L., 4 items (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Drechsler, C., 2 items (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Dreymann, C., 2 items (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Dubos, R.J., 3 items (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Dubuar-Rooney Co., 2 items (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Duffield, E.T. Recommendation for Mr. Teuscher, 1 item (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Duffy, C.E., 1 item (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Duford, J.L., 1 item (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Duke, E., 2 items (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Dunbar, R. Recommendation for, 1 item (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Dunlap, A.A., 13 items (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Dunn, S., 3 items (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - duPont, Alfred Mrs., 8 items (Box 6, Folder 7)
      Recommendations for treatment of diseased trees and flowers. Includes letters of thanks from Mrs. duPont.
    - DuPorte, E.M., 1934 April; 5 items (Box 6, Folder 7)
      Meeting: Quebec Society for the Protection of Plants meeting. Paper delivered "Recent advances in studies on plant virus diseases"
    - Durham, E.J., 1 item (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Durrell, L.W., 3 items (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Dykstra, T.P., 3 items (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Dunn, C.G., 2 items (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Dodge, B.O., 1931-1946; 48 items (Box 6, Folder 8)
      Professional Correspondence between colleagues socially friendly. Includes comments on NAS elections.
    - Doehlert, C.A., 1947-1955; 58 items (Box 6, Folder 9)
      Professional Correspondence between colleagues socially friendly. Includes 7 items Correspondence with P.E. Marucci.
  - E (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Eames, A.J., 2 items
    - Earl, W.H., 2 items
    - East, E.M., 2 items
      Includes recommendation for T.E. Rawlins for research grant.
    - Eastman, M.G., 2 items
    - Edgecombe, A.E., 2 items
    - Edgerton, C.W., 4 items
    - Edsall, D.L., 2 items
    - Ehrlich, J., 27 items
    - Eide, C.J., 2 items
    - Eimer and Amend, 8 items
    - Einhorn, S., 3 items
    - Elek, A., 5 items
    - Elliott, C., 1 item
    - Elmer, O.H., 6 items
    - Elrod, R.P. 1941-1947 at RIMR, 1939-1947; 33 items
      Includes Elrod Curriculum vitae and 1939-47 bibliography; recommendation for army commission.
    - Elsasser, T., 2 items
    - Emmons, C.W., 2 items
    - Emsweller, S.L., 1 item
    - Engstrom, E.W., 2 items
    - Entomological Society of America., 1937 December 28; 2 items
      Meeting: American Assoc of Economic Entomologists/Entomotogical Soc of America symposium paper delivered
    - Eny, D.M., 2 items
    - Esau, K., 5 items
    - Everitt, K.V., 1 item
    - Eyster, H.C., 4 items
  - F-Fi (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Fajardo, T.G., 1 item
    - Farber, L., 2 items
    - Faris, J.A., 2 items
    - Faulkner, E.H., 2 items
    - Faull, J.H., 2 items
    - Fay, D.J., 5 items
    - Fay, R.W., 17 items
      Includes curriculum vitae and Fay et al reprints and abstract of Fay thesis.
    - Feder, S.A., 10 items
      Includes curriculum vitae and graduate record transcript.
    - Felber, I., 7 items
      Includes curriculum vitae.
    - Felt, E.P., 2 items
    - Fenne, S.B., 7 items
    - Ferdinandsen, C., 4 items
    - Ferguson, M.C., 2 items
    - Fernholz, M.E., 1 item
    - Fernow, K.H., 4 items
    - Feusier, M.L., 1 item
    - Fifth Pacific Science Congress, 11 items
      Includes revised program of papers and authors. [Dr. Kunkel does not submit paper or attend].
  - Fi-Fr (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Fink, C.G., 2 items
    - Fink, H.C., 2 items
    - Finlay, A., 2 items
    - Finley, A.M., 1 item
    - Fisher, J.B., 2 items
    - Fitz, G.W., 4 items
    - Fitzpatrick, R.E., 1 item
    - Flanagan, F., 2 items
    - Flemer, Wm., 2 items
    - Fleu, C.B., 8 items
    - Flint, W.P. Meeting, 1937 December 28; 10 items
      Most Correspondence about 1937 Dec 28 Indianapolis, Ind. Joint symposium by the Entomological Society of America/American Assoc of Economic Entomologists on the relationship between insects and plant diseases. Paper delivered "Insects in relation to diseases of fruit trees and small fruits".
    - Florists' Review, 1931 1941; 4 items
    - Flory, L.P., 1 item
    - Foreman, M.O., 2 items
    - Fowl, J. Inc., 1 item
    - Foxboro Co., 2 items
    - Frampton, V.L., 4 items
    - Francis. T. Jr. Meeting, 1934 February 23; 7 items
      Includes Correspondence about 1934 Feb 23 RIMR staff meeting. Paper delivered "The pathology and biology of peach yellows" with typescript of abstract of presentation.
    - Frank, A., 4 items
    - Frazier, N.W., 11 items
    - Frazier, W.A., 1 item
    - Freas Thermo-Electric Co., 13 items
      Includes blueprints of Freas electric germinator cabinet.
    - Fred, E.B., 3 items
      Includes recommendations for F.A. Haasis, J.H. Freitag, G.L. McNew, C.E. Yarwood.
    - Free, M., 4 items
    - Free Press Printing Co., 5 items
  - Fr-Fu (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Freeman, A.W., 1936 January 21; 12 items
      Address: Baltimore, Md. Johns Hopkins University DeLamar lecture. Paper delivered "Virus diseases in plants"
    - Freeman, E.M., 2 items
    - Freeman, M.E., 2 items
    - Freitag, J.H., 3 items
    - Friedewald, W.F., 2 items
    - Friedman, B.A., 4 items
    - Frison, T.H., 1937; 4 items
      Meeting: 1937 (?) Location (?) Paper delivered "Insects in relation to diseases of fruit trees and small fruits"
    - Froehlich, M.L., 2 items
    - Fromme, F.D., 1932; 24 items
      Professional Correspondence between colleagues socially friendly with photograph of Barbara Fromme (daughter).
      Includes Meetings: of the American Phytopathological Society: 1932 Atlantic City, N.J.;. 1933 December Boston, MA; 1934 December Pittsburgh, PA; 1936 December Atlantic City, NJ; 1937 December Indianapolis, IN.
    - Fujimaki, Y., 1 item
    - Fry and Edwards, 1 item
    - Fukushi, T., 2 items
    - Fulton, H.R., 3 items
    - Fulton, L., 3 items
    - Fulton, R.H., 4 items
    - Fulton, R.W., 1940-1957; 13 items
    - Funke, G.L., 3 items
    - Furth, J., 1 item
  - G-Ge (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Gaby, W.L., 2 items
    - Gaddis, B.M., 6 items
    - Gaertner, E.E., 5 items
    - Gager, C.S., 1935-1942; 17 items
      Meeting. Includes Correspondence about 1935 May 15 Brooklyn Botanical Gardens 25 anniversary celebration. Paper delivered "Virus diseases of plants - 25 years of progress 1910-1935".
    - Ganguly, A., 2 items
    - Gansel, A.E., 6 items
    - Garber, R.J., 2 items
    - Gardner, M.W., 1931-1953 March; 26 items
      Includes recommendation for H.T. Osborn; 1 item Correspondence about 1953 Mar Ithaca, Cornell University lectures on virus diseases.
    - Gardner, V.R., 3 items
    - Garner, R.L., 2 items
    - Gassner, G., 2 items
    - Gates, R.R., 2 items
    - Gamann, E., 8 items
    - Gow, H.Z., 6 items
    - Geiling, E.M.K., 2 items
    - General Education Board., 3 items
      Fellowship recommendation for W.J. Youden
    - Georgia Agricultural Experiment Station, 1 item
    - Gerstel, D.U., 2 items
  - Gh-Gr (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Ghosh, C., 4 items
    - Gibson, K.E., 1 item
    - Gibson, R.E., 1 item
    - Giddings, N.J., 1933-1954; 7 items
    - Gilbert, E.M., 4 items
    - Gilman, J.C., 3 items
    - Gilmer, R.M., 5 items
    - Girolami, G., 2 items
    - Gladstone, S., 2 items
    - Glasstone, V.F., 29 items
    - Glick, D.P., 2 items
    - Glick, R., 2 items
    - Gloster, C., 3 items
    - Glover, N., 2 items
    - Godfrey, G.H. Meeting, 1932-1947; 22 items
      Includes 1 item Correspondence about 1946 Dec. Boston, AAAS meeting. Paper delivered "on incubation period of corn stunt virus in Baldulus maidis".
    - Goebel, W.F. Meeting, 1932 1944; 5 items
      Includes 1932 Apr 1 RIMR staff meeting. Presentation "Some types of plant diseases"; letter of congratulation to W.F. Goebel on becoming RIMR Member.
    - Goehde, H.L. von, 2 items
    - Goheen, A.C., 2 items
    - Goldfarb, A.J., 1 item
    - Goodman, J.J., 2 items
    - Gordon, M.A., 1 item
    - Goss, R.W., 2 items
    - Gottlieb, D., 1 item
    - Gotz, M.B., 3 items
    - Gould, C.J., 1 item
    - Gould, D.J., 2 items
    - Gowen, J.W., 2 items
    - Graham, K.M., 1 item
    - Grainger, J., 1 item
    - Grandfield, C.O., 2 items
    - Granick, S., 2 items
      Granick holograph reporting observations on the mosaic-affected leaves
    - Granovsky, A.A., 11 items
  - Gr-Gy (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Grant, T.J., 38 items
    - Gravatt, G.F., 5 items
    - Gray, J.A., 1938; 2 items
      Meeting: Correspondence about 1938 Summer Ottawa symposium. Paper delivered on tobacco mosaic
    - Greathouse, G.A., 2 items
    - Gricevicius, J.G., 1 item
    - Griffith, F., 2 items
    - Grimble, J.G., 1 item
    - Groff, G.W., 1 item
    - Gross, L., 5 items
    - Gross, P., 3 items
    - Grove, C.C., 3 items
    - Groves, A.B., 6 items
    - Gruessner, E., 2 items
    - Guba, E.F., 4 items
    - Guenther, Dr., 2 items
    - Guggenheim, John Simon Memorial Foundation, 1937-1960; 21 items
      Includes Guggenheim fellowship recommendations for: Drs. Rosene, J.T. Medlar, A.S. Costa, J.G. Bald, K. Maramorosch, F. Ross; also pamphlet listing 1959 Guggenheim Fellows.
    - Gssow, H.T., 8 items
    - Gustafson, F.G., 2 items
      Gustafson evaluation of Sam Granick for possible RIMR position
    - Guterman, C.E.F., 1931-1936 1949; 25 items
      Includes recommendation for Lindsay M. Black.
    - Gye, W.E., 1 item
  - H-Ha
    - Haasis, F.A., 2 items (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Haenseler, C.M., 5 items (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Hall, J.K., 2 items (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Hallauer, C., 1 item (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Hamilton, C.C., 4 items (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Hamilton Hotel, 1 item (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Hammett, F.S., 2 items (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Hammon, W. McD, 2 items (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Hanna, W.F., 1 item (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Hansen, H.P., 2 items (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Hardison, J.R., 4 items (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Harris, H.A., 2 items (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Harris, J. Co., 1 item (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Harris, M.M., 4 items (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Harris, R.V., 1933 1949; 5 items (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Harrison, A.L. (3) (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Hart, H. (Editor-in-Chief of Phytopathology), 6 items (Box 8, Folder 1)
      Includes recommendation for L.M. Black to serve on editorial board of Phytopathology.
      Related Materials
      (See under: Humphrey, H.B. Box no. 7 for earlier Phytopathology correspondence)
    - Hartley, C., 1931-1936; 35 items (Box 8, Folder 1)
      Includes 2 photographs of a specimen of brooming disease of locust.
      Professional Correspondence between colleagues